www.tvsubtitles.net
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
11x04 "便弹"
Episode 11x04 "The Snuke"
各位同学都坐好了.
All right, students, let's take our seats.
大家都友好一些, 今天我们有新同学加入.
Everyone try to be nice because we have a new student joining us today
希望大家能给他一个好印象.
and I know you'll all make him feel welcome.
大家欢迎 Bahir Hassan Abdul Hakeem.
Say hello to Bahir Hassan Abdul Hakeem.
欢迎来到我们班, Bahir. - 谢谢.
Welcome to our class, Bahir. - Thank you.
不妙啊!
Dude, not cool!
先坐到Kyle那儿的空位子上吧.
Why don't you take a seat in Kyle's empty desk for now?
好的.
Okay.
Eric, 你他妈怎么了?! 怎么回事?
Eric, what the hell is wrong with you?! - What's wrong?
他被查过没炸弹吧? - Eirc, 不许胡闹!
Has he been checked for bombs? - Eric, that's enough!
并不是所有的穆斯林人都是恐怖分子!
Not all muslim people are terrorists!
对, 但大部分是. 并且他们占恐怖分子的大部分.
No, but most of them are. And all it takes is most of them.
轮你了, Bahir.
Now you go, Bahir.
喂? - Kyle, 你在用电脑吗?
Yeah? - Kyle, are you on your computer?
啊? 没有, 我病了. - 快上网.
What? No, I'm sick. - Get online.
我需要你给我查点东西. - 老兄, 别烦我.
I need you to check something for me. - Dude, leave me alone.
Kyle, 我们的每个朋友可能都身处险境!
Kyle, every one of our friends might be in serious danger!
啊? 为什么? - 现在快上网!
What? Why? - Get online now!
好的, 好的.
All right, all right.
上MySpace, 看看 有没有一个是Bahir Hakeem的.
Go to MySpace. See if there's a MySpace page for a Bahir Hakeem.
"Bahir Hakeem."
芝加哥出生, 8岁, 最喜欢绿色.
Born in Chicago, eight years old, his favorite color is green.
Cartman, 这是干什么?
Cartman, what is this all about?
Kyle, 我要你查查他的好友列表, 他有多少个MySpace好友?
Kyle, I want you to check his buddy list. How many MySpace friends does he have?
超过一百.
Over a hundred.
接着看到底. 有没有写他最喜欢的乐队?
Look further down the page. Does he list his favorite band?
White Stripes.
有趣. - 什么?
That's funny. - What?
今天他和班上的人说 他最喜欢的乐队是Blink 182.
He told everyone in class today his favorite band was Blink 182.
接下来的故事发生在 课间休息和地理课之间.
The following takes place between recess and Geography class.
喂?
Hello?
Barbrady长官, 南方公园小学现在十分危险!
Officer Barbrady, South Park Elementary is in serious danger!
为什么? 你是谁?
From what? Who is this?
我刚刚查一个穆斯林人, 发现他与MySpace上描述不符.
I've just ID'd a muslim and his MySpace page does not check out.
你现在要让人们都马上撤出来!
You've got to get these people out of here now!
你当真?
Are you serious?
如果我不认真的话, 我会这样说话吗?
If I wasn't serious, would I be talking like this?
怎样说话?
Like what?
低沉耳语, 但是声音却很大, 为了有很强的震撼力.
Whispering, but whispering really loudly for dramatic effect.
这样啊.
Oh jeez.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
所有学生马上撤离学校!
All students are to evacuate the school immediately!
嘿, Bahir, 我们都下课了, 要不要到我家下象棋?
Hey, Bahir, since we get to go home, you wanna come over, play checkers?
行啊. - 好的!
Sure, okay. - Allright!
老兄啊.
Dude.
喂!
Yeah.
Stan给我发了消息说 他们都撤离学校了.
Dude, I just got an IM from Stan that they evacuated the school.
嗯. 现在你相信我的那些话了吧?
Yeah. Now do you believe me that something is going on?!
我想是. -对, 但是还有问题! 感觉不对!
I guess so. - Yeah, well I don't like it! It doesn't follow!
感觉什么不对? -为什么恐怖分子只来炸学校?
What doesn't follow? - Why would a terrorist just blow up a school?
这不是他们的作风. 除非...
It's not their M.O. Unless...
天! 除非这只是为了转移视线!
Oh my God! Unless this was all just a big diversion.
Kyle, 你马上Google搜索南方公园商会!
Kyle, I need you to Google-search the South Park Chamber of Commerce!
好的.
Okay.
他们的网站有日历记事, 今天有什么大活动?!
Their website should have a calendar of events, is there anything big going on in town today?!
有, 有一个... - 什么啊!
Yeah. Actually, there is. - What?
希拉里-克林顿的竞选拉票会.
There's a Hillary Clinton campaign rally.
Cartman?
长官! 有人打电话进来 说将有一起恐怖袭击.
Sir! There's somebody calling in saying there's going to be a terrorist attack
就在今天的希拉里-克林顿竞选拉票会.
on the Hillary Clinton rally today.
什么? 我是CIA总局长, Alan Thompson.
What? This is CIA head, Alan Thompson.
Thompson先生, 你必须取消今天的克林顿拉票会!
Mr. Thompson, you have to call off the Clinton rally!
南方公园有恐怖分子!
There's a terrorist in South Park!
你知道什么?
What do you know?
出乎预料突然出现! 我要马上和总统通话!
He just showed up out of the blue! I need to speak with the President right away!
我是CIA局长! 你可以和我讲! 我说我只和总统讲!
I'm the head of the CIA! You can tell me! - I said I will only talk to the President!
听着, 如果你有详细的信息, 你可以-
Look, if you have information of a threat, you could-
我将逮捕你-
I will have you arrested for-
我听不见你说! 只要总统!
I can't hear you! Only the president!
电话转接过来了, 总统先生.
Call is coming through now, Mr. President.
喂? - 布什总统, 我是Eric Cartman!
Hello? - President Bush, this is Eric Cartman!
我们通话安全吗? 什么? 谁?
Are we on a secure line? - Huh? Who.
听着, 我知道你不是最大的Hildog迷, 但她现在确实处境危险!
Look, I know you're not the biggest Hildog fan, but she is in great danger right now!
Hildog?
是, 我明白. 我会转告给克林顿女士的.
Yes, I understand. I'll let Ms. Clinton know.
什么事, Brian?
What is it, Brian?
克林顿夫人, 我们刚刚收到消息说 今天你的拉票会上会有恐怖袭击.
Ms. Clinton, we just received word of a possible terrorist attack on your rally today.
消息确凿?
Is the thread credible?
我们还不确定, 但是也许 我们最好取消这次集会.
We aren't sure, but perhaps it's best we call it off.
不不, 我不会被恐怖分子的威胁所吓倒.
No. No, I will not be bullied by terrorist threats.
你们都做的很好, Brian.
Your men do a good job, Brian.
我相信所有的威胁都会被妥善处理.
I have faith that any thread will be taken care of accordingly.
我们到集会场地了, Hildog.
We've reached the rally site, Hildog.
别担心, 克林顿夫人, 我确信不会有意外发生.
Don't worry, Mrs. Clinton, I'm sure everything will be fine.
谢谢, Cris.
Thank you, Chris.
他们知道了炸弹! - 不可能!
They know about the bomb! - That is impossible!
我们做了各种测试确保炸弹的隐蔽性.
We took every measure to assure the bomb was hidden from sight.
有人给CIA透信的.
Well somebody tipped off the CIA.
我不知道他们了解多少, 但是安全检查已经被增强了.
I don't know how much they know, but security has been heightened.
那个炸弹必须随克林顿 拉票一直到波士顿的!
That bomb must travel with the Clinton rally to Boston!
现在炸弹运不到波士顿了!
The bomb won't make it to Boston now!
高强度安检下, 时间不多就会找到炸弹.
With the heightened security, it's only a matter of time before they find it!
这样我们别无选择, 我们只有提前袭击了.
Then we have no choice. We have to move up the attack.
我明白, 同志. - 准备吧.
I understand, comrade. - Prepare yourself.
我们一小时后引爆炸弹.
We detonate the bomb within the hour.
Kyle, 我在克林顿集会场, 但是没发现那个小孩!
Kyle, I'm at the Clinton rally site, but there's no sign of that kid!
所有有些事情还是不对. - 不, 我没错.
So then maybe you're wrong. - Nope, I'm not wrong.
他一定在他家里通过什么手段来远程攻击. 找到地址了吗?
He must be somehow attacking remotely from his house. Did you find the address?
对, 我看了他的MySpace 和realtor.com的交叉引用.
Yeah. I cross-referenced his MySpace page with realtor.com.
他父母搬到了Janice街的绿房子里.
His parents moved into that green house on Janice Street.
天, 在城的另一边.
Jesus, that's on the other side of town.
好了, Kyle, 我要用我带摄像的 手机拍张照片上传给你.
All right, Kyle, I'm going to take a picture with my camera phone and upload it to you.
准备好了吗? - 好了.
You ready? - Yeah.
这是什么? - 是我的球!
What is that? - It's my balls!
去你妈的Cartman!
Goddamnit Cartman!
好了,好了, Kyle, 我们还是回到正题.
Okay. Okay, Kyle, let's stay focused here.
南方公园的市民, 我非常荣幸的有请 一位非常令人尊敬的女人.
People of South Park, it is my honor to introduce a woman who deserves nothing but respect.
希拉里-罗德姆-克林顿夫人!
Mrs. Hillary Rodham Clinton!
回到像自己出生地一样的小城 是如此的令人愉快.
It is so nice to be back in a small town like the one I came from.
Hildog!
Otis Green, 关于炸弹有何消息?
Otis Green, anything on that bomb threat?
我们正派嗅炸弹的反恐猪穿过人群.
We have the bomb-smiffing pig going through the crowd.
如果有炸弹, 反恐猪就会发现.
If there is a bomb, the pig will find it.
这就是我来这样的小城宣讲的原因.
This is why I campaign in small towns like these!
因为在南方公园这样的城市 你能找到正真的美国.
Because it is in towns like South Park that you find the true America!
天啊, 她闻到了气味! - 什么?
Oh my God, she got a scent! - What?!
猪闻到了核武器留下的气味.
The pig is picking up the smell of nuclear residue.
恐怖分子藏有炸弹!
Terrorists have hidden a bomb!
天! 哪里?! 他们可能把它藏在哪里?
Oh my God! Where?! Where could they have stashed it?!
继续, 找到它, 找啊!
Come on, find it. Find!
天, 他们藏在了讲台下?
My God, they hid it under the stage?!
不是, 看.
No wait, look.
我们在无谓的花销上浪费了多少钱?
How much money do we have to waste on needless spending
当我们应该全力关注...
when we should be focusing all our attention on...
关于教育...
on the education of all-
别闹, 小孩.
There, girl.
关于下一代的教育.
On the education of all children.
哦, 我申明!
Oh, I declare!
老天, 你认为他们会把 核武器藏在克林顿夫人的...
Oh my God. Do you think they could have hidden a nuclear device up Mrs. Clinton's...
Thompson先生, 那个电话报警的小孩说的是对的!
Mr. Thompson, the kid who called in the warning was right!
我们发现恐怖分子有核武器
We uncovered intel that terrorists have obtained a nuclear device
似乎就藏在克林顿夫人的...
and that they have most likely hidden it in Mrs. Clinton's...
在她的... - 在她哪儿?
Well, in her... - In her what?
在她"下面", 长官. - 啥?!
In her snatch, sir. - What?!
怎么了? 我还没有讲完.
What is going on? I wasn't finished.
安检, 克林顿夫人. 也许没什么事.
Security measure, Mrs. Clinton. Probably nothing.
嗯?
Yes?
Jeffries先生, 我是CIA的Alan Thompson.
Mr. Jeffries, this is Alan Thompson with the CIA.
我们确信克林顿夫人 身上安有核弹, 安在她"下面".
We have reason to believe that Mrs. Clinton may have a nuclear device up her snatch.
是什么? - 是"下面".
A what?! - A snatch.
是阴道的术语. - 不, 我是问什么样的核弹.
It's the technical term for vagina. - No, I mean what kind of nuclear device?!
Jeffries先生, 我是Frank Waters.
Mr. Jeffries, this is Frank Waters.
这是一种便携核弹, 适合安放在女性"下面", 叫做"便弹".
It's a suitcase nuke, designed to fit in a woman's snizz. It's called a snuke.
怎样了, Brian?
What is going on, Brian?
克林顿女士, 恐怖分子 在你的下边下了个"便弹".
Ms. Clinton, it appears that terrorists have snuck a snuke up your snizz.
哦.
Oh my.
我们怎么办? 我们能停掉倒计时吗? - 它没有计时器.
What can we do? Can we disable the timer? - It won't have a timer.
"便弹"会被远程引爆. 恐怖分子之中有人控制着引爆器.
Snukes are detonated remotely. Whoever our terrorist is has a detonator with him.
意思是说...
But then that means...
对, 如果我们找不到引爆器, 南方公园的每个人都必死无疑.
Yes. If we don't find that detonator, everyone in the town of South Park is going to die.
永远消失.
Forever.
我们跟踪那电话了吗? - 电话进来了, 长官.
Do we have that phone trace? - The call is going through now, sir.
喂? - 我是CIA局长Alan Thompson.
Yeah? - This is CIA head Alan Thompson.
我们之前通过话- - 对, Thompson先生?
We spoke before about the- - Yes, Mr. Thompson?
我们刚刚到达你们城市. - 为什么, 你找什么东西?
Well, we've just arrived in your town. - Why? Did you find something?
对. 克林顿女士下边安有便携核弹.
Yes. There's a suitcase nuke in Ms. Clinton's snizz.
便弹? - 对.
A snuke? - That's right.
被远程遥控的.
It's controlled by a remote detonator.
我们必须在引爆前找到恐怖分子.
We have to locate the terrorist before he sets it off.
我有恐怖分子搬家的地址.
I have the address of the house the terrorist moved into.
我就要到了, 你在哪里?
I'm almost there now, where are you?
我在市主道上, 冰激凌店边.
We're on the town's main street, right by an ice cream shop.
老兄, 我在你旁边.
Oh dude, I'm, I'm right next to you.
嘿
Oh, hey.
今天我们都被赶出学校了 - 我知道, 有大事.
Dude, we totally got let out of school. - I know. Something big is going on.
看这个. 我用Google搜索 "希拉里克林顿选票会",
Take a look at this. I did a Google search for "Hillary Clinton Campaign Rally" right?
一个链接到YouTube, 这个俄国人有很多视频.
And one of the links was to YouTube, where this Russian guy had a bunch of videos.
俄国人? - 对, 就他, Vladimir Stolfsky.
Russian? - Yeah, this guy, Vladimir Stolfsky.
他有每个集会的视频. - 他着迷希拉里-克林顿.
He had videos on YouTube of every single rally. - So he's a Hillary Clinton fan.
错, 我查了他YouTube 和MySpace的交叉引用.
No. I cross-referenced his YouTube profile with MySpace
并且根据他的Blog发现, 他是守旧派的共产主义者.
and according to his blog, he's an old-school Communist.
所以他在希拉里的每个集会上干什么?
So what's he doing at every Clinton rally?
用WebCrawler搜搜, 也许有他的Podcast(播客).
Do a WebCrawler search, maybe he has podcasts up somewhere.
好主意.
Oh that's a good idea.
怎么了? 我们犯什么了?
What is going on? What have we done?
他们声称自己不知道什么袭击.
They claim they don't know anything about an attack.
有意思!
Big surprise!
长官, 第一次搜查完毕, 未发现"便弹"引爆器.
Sir, first pass of the house, we didn't find a snuke detonator anywhere.
你儿子在哪里?
We thought he was at school.
我们以为他在学校. 他不在学校?
We thought he was at school. He's not at school?
不要紧张, 克林顿女士. - 他们知道多长吗, Brian?
You're doing great, Ms. Clinton. - Do they know how long, Brian?
多长时间后我下面的"便弹"会被拆除?
How long before the snuke in my snizz goes off?
他们会找到引爆器的, Hildog.
They'll find the detonator, Hildog.
我们不能干等他们找引爆器.
We can't wait for them to find the detonator.
如果我们能靠近炸弹, 或许就能拆除它.
If we can get to the bomb, maybe we can deactivate it.
就没有人能到 克林顿夫人下面看看吗?
Can't somebody go and take a loo inside Mrs. Clinton's snizz?
我是不会派我的人进去的.
I'm not sending any of my men in there.
你准备引爆炸弹了吗?
Are you almost ready to set off the bomb?
一切正常, 引爆器计时进行中.
Everything is set. We have the detonator up and running.
Hakeem先生, 告诉我们你孩子在哪里! - 我说了, 不知道.
Mr. Hakeem, we need to know where your son is! - I tell you, I do not know.
这样下去没有进展. 他知道也不会说.
This is getting us nowhere. If he knows anything, he's not saying.
让我和他谈谈. - 你做什么?
Let me have time with him. - What are you going to do?
我们必须找到引爆器! 让我和他谈谈!
We have to find that detonator! Let me have time with him!
你会告诉我你儿子在哪里! - 他应该在学校!
You will tell me where your son is! - He should be at school!
嘿!
Hey!
引爆器在哪儿?! - 什么引爆器-
Where is the detonator?! - What detonator are you ta-
我可以一整天这样. - 我什么都不知-
I can do this all day. - I don't know anything about a-
停了, 别! - 你可以让我停的.
Stop it! Really! - You can make it stop!
我没有那-
I don't have the-
我们就这样继续吗?
Are we just gonna let this go on?
我找到了那俄国人的Podcast. 上面有很多eBay链接.
Okay, I got a text of the Russian guy's podcast. It's all a bunch of links to eBay.
你应该搜搜他在eBay的用户名, 看看他都有什么买卖.
You should be able to search his username on eBay and see what he's been buying and selling.
Ferris, 架在那边. 你们俩去床那边.
Ferris, set up over there. Two of you can take that bed area.
嘿! - Donner, 接管那个工作站.
Hey! - Donner, take over that station.
怎么了?
What's going on?
此住处已被国安局征用.
This apartment is being absorbed by Homeland Security!
国安局?
Homeland Security?
你们在人事上玩的小把戏结束了.
Look, your little game of going over people's heads is over!
你们还可以继续工作, 但是现在起一切听我指挥, 明白?
You could still work, but from now on you answer to me, you got that?!
请问, 这里谁负责?! - 我!
Excuse me, who's in charge here?! - I am!
那现在不归你管了. 此处刚被分配给FBI.
Yeah well not anymore you're not. This apartment has just been assigned to the FBI.
荒谬, 谁下的令?! - 国防部长的命令!
That's outrageous! On whose orders?! - On order of the Secretary of Defense!
你一边去, 现在我负责!
You had your shot, now I'm in charge!
现在不归你们管了! 中央刚刚下令!
Not anymore you're not! Orders just came down from Central!
他们要ATF在第一位置处理!
They want ATF handling this on all fronts!
现在起, 大家全部听我指挥!
All right people, from now on you're answering to me!
现在不归他们管了! 总统刚刚下令!
Not anymore they're not! Orders from the President.
他要自己单独处理此事! 现在Nelson我负责.
He wants this handled by his staff personally! Now Nelson is in charge.
现在起不归我管了.
Not anymore I'm not!
你要对我妻子做什么? 你说出你儿子去向就没事.
What are you going to do to my wife?! - Nothing if you tell me where your son is!
我们说了, 不知道啊.
We told you, we don't know.
知道这是什么啊?
Do you know what this is?!
这是苹果汁. 能让我造出超级臭屁.
This is apple juice. It gives super bad farts.
他刚把苹果汁打给自己了?
Did he just inject himself with apple juice?
你儿子在哪?! - 她也不知道.
Where is your son?! - She doesn't know either.
我认真的! 停了! 很恶心! 你妈妈在哪里?
I mean it! Stop! That is disgusting! Where is your mother?!
接电话!
Answer it!
喂? Bahir. 你在哪儿?
Hallo? Hallo Bahir. Where are you?
谁是Butters? - Butters.
Who it Butters? - Butters.
Bahir, 你一个同学挟持我们做人质.
Bahir, one of your classmates is keeping us hostage.
你这个龌龊的小流氓!
You filthy little rapscallion!
找到了! 我知道他在哪儿! - 哪里?我们派人过去!
We got him! I know where he is! - All right, where? We'll send our people in.
不, 他是我的. - 你不能独自去.
No no, he's my lead. - You're not going alone.
你们冒险把他逮捕搜查 却没有发现引爆器!
You blow in there and you risk taking him down without finding the detonator!
我要去找到它在哪里!
I'm going to find out where it is!
大家现在归我管, 我们会找到恐怖分子的.
All right, people, I'm in charge now and we will find the terrorists.
Jarvis, 我要你查 AOL上所有的恐怖聊天分子.
Jarvis, I want you to check for any terrorist chatter on AOL.
Marley 和 Greggs, 在askjeeves.com上搜核武器.
Marley and Greggs, try searching for nuclear devices on askjeeves.com.
AskJeeves? 没人用AskJeeves! 用Google去搜!
Ask Jeeves? Nobody uses Ask Jeeves! Just Google-search it!
教我怎么干活? - 对!
Are you telling me how to do my job? - Yes.
有个俄国人叫Vladimir Stolfsky.
There's a Russian guy named Vladimir Stolfsky
搜索引擎几乎全部命中.
who's got search engine hits all over this thing.
Chase, 在YouTube上搜索Stolfsky, 并检查与JDate的链接!
Chase, search the name Stolfsky on YouTube and cross-reference it with JDate!
在查...
Checking.
看, 这些俄国人都在Blog上讨论这事.
Look, these Russian guys all have blogs talking about this
似乎这只是大的转移, 背后有着更大的隐情.
like it's just some big diversion for something much bigger!
长官, 孩子们说的对. 我们刚刚获得情报
Sir, these kids are right. We've just received intel that Russian terrorists
那个俄罗斯人就是 这起恐怖袭击的幕后黑手.
are believed to be responsible for the threat.
消息来源是哪里? - 我们在Drudge Report站点看到的.
Where's the intel from? - We just read it on Drudge Report.
我们已经找到那家伙的Blog了.
Look, we already have the guy's blog.
或许我们能通过MapQuest网站找到地址.
Maybe we can find an address and check it out on MapQuest.
要按我的方式做! 我是主管!
We do this my way! I'm the one in charge!
这里不归你管了. 噢, 算了.
Not anymore you're not. - Oh, snap.
我又吃掉你一个棋子, Bahir.
I captured another one of your pieces, Bahir.
嘿Eric.
Oh hey Eric.
引爆器在哪儿? - 什么?
Where is the detonator! - The what?
你只有五秒时间, 否则我就冲你脸上放超臭的苹果汁屁!
You have exactly five seconds before I start dropping serious apple juice farts on your face!
一! - 放开我!
One! - Leave me alone!
别走!
Stop!
嘿, 我就要赢了的!
Hey, I was about to win!
站住, 恐怖分子, 我开枪了!
Stop, terrorist, or I will shoot you!
上车!
Get in the van!
虽然很酷但是我不玩了.
Uh, that's cool. I'm actually not playing anymore.
上车!
Get in the van!
没办法, 我们别无选择!
That's it! We don't have a choice anymore!
总要有人进去手动拆除"便弹"!
Somebody is going to have to go in and try to disarm the snuke manually!
不行, 太危险了! 她下面已经30多年没动静.
No, it's too dangerous! That snatch has not seen action in over 30 years!
可能有毒气之类.
It could be toxic!
我来. 我去检查克林顿女士的下面.
I'll do it! I'll check out Ms. Clinton's snizz.
放我走吧! 我只是小孩子!
Let me go! Please! I am just a little boy!
你电话报警给政府 泄露了我们的行动.
You called and warned the government of our plans!
你不知道的是 我们仅仅是雇佣兵.
What you don't know is that we are merely mercenaries!
我们被收买去安核弹, 等真正的敌人来进攻.
We were paid to set up the snuke so that the real enemy of America could attack!
酷, 我很欢迎穆斯林人入侵.
That's cool. I'm fine with muslims invading.
你真的以为穆斯林人 是这起恐怖袭击的幕后?
You really think Muslims are behind this terrorist threat?!
对啊?
Uh yes, of course?
美国在穆斯林之前有其他敌人, 谁是美国最先的敌人?
America had other enemies before the Muslims, you know. Who is America's oldest enemy?
俄国? - 之前.
The Russians? - Before that.
德国? - 之前.
The Germans? - Before that.
又是德国? - 之前!
The Germans again? - Before that!
我说的是美国最最先的敌人! 众所周知的美国大敌!
I am talking about the oldest threat to America! The greatest enemy America has ever known!
该不会是...
You can't possible mean...
200年, 终于等到了. 我们就要把叛徒抓回给国王了!
Two hundred years we've waited. Finally. We will get those traitors to the Crown!
陛下?
Yes, Your Majesty?
俄国人要引爆炸弹转移视线了.
The Russians are ready to set off the diversion.
全速航行!
Full sail.
全速航行, 陛下.
Full sail, your Majesty.
好了, Brian.
All right, Brian, this is it.
进到克林顿女士下面, 看看能不能拆除"便弹".
Get in there and see if you can disarm the snuke in Ms. Clinton's snatch.
好了, 正在接近下面.
All right. I'm nearing her snizz now.
上帝保佑.
God help him.
你看到什么了, Brian? - 这里又黑, 又冷.
What do you see, Brian? - It's dark. Cold.
做的好, Brian. 尽量靠近. 看里面.
You're doing fine, Brian. Get as close as you can. You have to look inside the snizz.
正在看.
Allright, I'm,looking.
嗯, 看到了... 我看到武器了!
Yes, I see... I see the device!
做的棒, Brian, 顶住.
You're doing great, Brian. Hang in there.
嗯, 金属外壳, 有种三岔触点的装置...
There's um, metal housing some kind of three-pronged triggering mechanism that...
等等, 还有别的东西!
Wait there's something else here!
有个...
There's something...
重复一下, Brian.
Say again, Brian.
有个东西爬在"便弹"的线圈上.
There's something perched on the snuke's coil.
天, 它正看着我!
Oh God, it's looking at me!
Brian, 快出来! - 你是什么?!
Brian, get out of there! - What are you?!
我可不怕你! 退后! 退后-
I have no qualm with you! Stay back! Stay back I-
Brian? Brian 怎么了? - 它吃我头! 它吃我头!
Brian? Brian, what's happening? - It's eating my head! It's eating my head!
呀!
Oh my!
找到了!找到了!
I got it! I got it!
根据PayPal, 那些俄国人只是雇佣兵.
According to PayPal, the Russian guys are just hired mercenaries
他们在Craig's List站点上有广告, 通过eBay付的款.
who had ads up on Craig's List and got paid through eBay.
这样人们就可能会被英国人袭击.
So that person could be attacked by the British.
英国人? - 忠实的红衣兵.
The British? - Loyalist Red Coats!
长官, 我找到了俄国人的eHarmony账户, 地址就在南方公园!
Sir, I found the Russian's eHarmony account! It does list an address in South Park!
好, MapQuest那个地址! 我会用GoogleMaps. 有及时交通状态.
All right! MapQuest the address! - I'll use Google Maps. It has live traffic.
脑子不错.
Good thinking.
长官, 我们找到了恐怖分子的基地. 正在发消息给你.
Sir, we have the terrorists' location. IM'ing you now.
很高兴认识你, 同志. - 想想你们的作为.
It was good knowing you, comrade. - Please. Think about what you are doing.
英国人利用你们, 你们会丧命的.
The British are just using you, you're going to die.
对, 但我们会有钱花.
Yes, but we will be rich.
左侧, 爆破, 安全! 冲!
Left flank, prig prang and clear! Go!
游戏结束了! 爬到地上! - 你们怎么找到的?
The game is over! Get down on the ground! - How did they find us?
我们无所不知! 你们帮红衣兵的诡计被识破了!
We know about everything! Your diversion to help the Red Coats is over!
没关系. 引爆器正在倒计时.
It doesn't matter. The detonator is on a timer.
你们太晚了! 只有三分钟!
You are too late! In three minutes!
他妈的?!
What the hell?!
停电了! - 那现在几点?
The power went out! - Well so then what time is it?
靠. - 拿下!
Oh crap. - Take 'em down!
别! 我还没有拿到钱!
No! I don't want to die without being paid!
引爆器被拆除, 将军. 你可以进来了.
The detonator is secured, general. You are cleared to proceed.
美国叛徒知道了我们的进攻?!
The Rebel Americans know of our attack?!
怎么会? - 自由射击!
How? - Fire at will!
啊?
Yes?
陛下, 进攻失败.
Your Majesty, the attack has failed.
我们没有能结束美国革命.
We were unable to end the American Revolution.
知道了.
I see.
看来我们拯救了我们国家, 避免再次被英帝国统治.
Well, looks like we saved our country from British rule once again.
对. 还证明了我们要学会 对人不要以偏概全.
Yeah. It just proves we need to learn not to profile one race of people.
因为, 说实话, 世界上多数人讨厌我们.
Because, actually, most of the world hates us.
Bahir, 我想我欠你一个道歉.
Well Bahir, I was thinking that maybe I owe you an apology.
真的? - 对.
Really? - Yes.
但我意识到, 技术上来说我不欠你.
But then I realized that technically, I don't.
因为我怀疑你, 才救了你一命, 救了大家.
Because by being suspicious of you I saved your life and everyone else's.
所以, 你欠我人情. 但是, 算了.
So really, you own me an apology. But that's cool.
你没有救大家, 我救的! 你只是在骚扰穆斯林!
You didn't save everyone, I did! You were just out harrassing muslims!
但如果不是我先 打电话给你让你查穆斯林.
But if I hadn't called you in the first place to check out the muslim
你还不是在床上病一天?
you would have just stayed in bed sick all day, right?
有可能. 可能?
Maybe. - Maybe?
如果我没打电话给你, 你就不会在电脑前查克林顿的拉票会.
If I hadn't called you, you wouldn't have been on your computer checking out the Clinton rally.
就是我对穆斯林的不能容忍, 才救了我们国家.
That means my intolerance of muslims saved America.
真是胡搅蛮缠.
That is so missing the point.
我顽强的阻止这次核弹爆炸, 是不是!
Me being a bigot stopped a nuclear bomb from going off, yes or no?!
话不能按你这么说- - 是不是, Kyle!
That's not the right way to look at it, I- - Yes or no, Kyle?!
不是! 不是你说的那样!
No! Not, not like you're saying.
但我还是会说: 今天, 顽强和种族歧视拯救了一切.
But that's all I'm saying: today, bigotry and racism saved the day.
Bahir, 明白吗?
Bahir, you get this, right?
Bahir, 离开那个恶心的小子! 回家收拾你的东西!
Bahir! Get away from that disgusting child! Get back home and start packing your things!
这个国家没法呆下去了!
We are leaving this whole intolerant country!
OK. 谁最终处理掉了穆斯林, 呃?
Okay. Who got rid of the Muslims, huh?
全是我. 说声谢谢就行了.
That was all me. Simple thank you will suffice.
Transcript: spscriptorium Sync: muter - forom.com
中文字幕翻译: Bi11
双语合成 Lv&daisy